Juan Portal

+1 (747) 294-7712 | juanportalg@gmail.com | California Github - LinkedIn / juanportal Portfolio: juanportalg.com

Summary

24 year old self taught developer. Seeking a Junior Front-End Developer job. Offering excellent organizational skills, communication and good judgment. Always trying to stay motivated by learning new things and looking for the overall success of the group. Currently learning React.

Skills

onstant deconstruction
С

CSS
Active communication

JavaScript
Customer Service

• Python • Flexible and adaptable

• Git • Organized

React
Conflict resolution

Experience

Front-End Web Developer | 07/2021 - Present | Freelance

- Building websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts.
- Improved customer service and telecommunication skills to build lasting relationships.

HTML Mailing | 10/2021 - Present | Freelance

- HTML Mailings for companies having in mind different devices, browsers and email services.
 - Maintained energy and enthusiasm in a fast-paced environment.

Owner | 06/2020 - Present | PKMarket

- eCommerce on eBay, selling virtual goods for games.
- Engaged customers in social conversations to create pleasant and easy shopping experience

Education

Mathematics | Universidad Nacional Mayor de San Marcos